The first product that I'm going to talk to about is a product called Egyptian Magic.
This is one of my favorite things to use for hair, skin, lips, soars, everything.
It's great.
Now when it comes to this product, the best quality about it is that it's all natural ingredients.
As you can see, it kind of starts out looking like a wax, but when you dig some out, you just stick it in your hand and then it melts slowly and turns into oil.
This makes it really easy to massage into a scalp and to run through somebodies hair. This, I really like to use in pretreatment.
If you rub a lot of this throughout the hair, it's kind of like a leave in conditioner and it keeps it moisturized throughout the whole braiding process.
That way it doesn't dry out anytime in the middle, but it's great for your skin.
Also, after braiding style is complete, it's good to just take a little bit and run it in between each braid.
Just to get that scalp extra happy and extra moisturized.
Since it's just been pulled on for an extended amount of time.